All right, so it's actually the appropriately named textSize
实际上 它与 textSize 属性名比较相称
that will make the text larger.
它将使得文本放大
Now maybe you thought it was textStyle.
也许你认为它是 textStyle
TextStyle is actually an attribute that's used for
TextStyle 其实是一个属性
changing text to either bold or italic.
用来将文本改变成粗体或斜体
But it doesn't change the size.
但是它不改变文本的大小
You might have been looking at textAlignment,
你可能会考虑 textAlignment
which does things like puts the text to the left of the view or
它会使得文本在视图中左对齐或
the right of the view, or centered in the view.
右对齐或居中显示
But it is actually textSize, so once we've determined this,
但是它实际上是 textSize 所以一旦我们确定了这一点
let's go ahead and make the changes in the code.
让我们在代码中做一些改变
All right, here I am, in my code.
这里是我的代码
I'm looking at activity main.xml like I always have been and
像之前一样 看activity main.xml
I'm going to scroll down so I can see my two TextViews.
然后向下滑动可以看到两个 TextView
Okay, So let's go ahead and add the attribute.
我们继续 添加属性
Put Android, the name of the attribute equals.
输入 android:textSize=
Okay, and now I have to put the value.
现在我必须输入一个值
And if you remember from the quiz question the value should be 36sp.
如果你记得问题 应该知道值为 36sp
As always, remember to have quotes around your value.
与往常一样 记得给值加上引号
And you're going to need android: before the value textSize.
在 textSize 值之前需要加上 android:
Oh yeah, and don't forget the equals sign.
不要忘记等号
Once you've done this, you should be able to go over here to the preview
一旦你做到这一点 你可以到这里
screen and see that the text has actually gotten bigger.
预览屏幕文本实际上已经变得更大了
Let's go ahead and make this text larger as well.
继续 使这个文本也变大
Okay, great.
太好了
And I've typed my textSize="36sp" here.
在这里输入 textSize="36sp"
And I see that it in fact, updated on the phone.
我看到它实际上更新了电话
But, in reality, this isn't your actual phone.
但是 这不是你真正的电话
So you should always, always,
所以你应该一直 一直
always run it on your phone to make sure it looks correct.
一直在你的手机上运行它来确保它看起来是正确的
To do that, I go up here to the green run button, select my phone and hit OK.
要做到这点 我往上点击绿色的运行按钮 选择我的手机 点击 OK
And good work, you've done it.
做的漂亮 你已经做到了
We no longer have small microtext, we have big and
小的文本已经变为大而
beautiful 36 sp text displayed on our phone.
美观的 36sp 的文本显示在手机上了
And just like that, we can check off text is much larger on our list.
就这样 我们可以划掉列表中的 text is much larger